Finding Aid for the Livingston Gearhart Papers, 1933-1997
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Livingston Gearhart Papers, 1933-1997
Mus. Arc. 23.1
Gearhart, Livingston
4 boxes ( 194 folders )
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The collection of Livingston Gearhart Papers contains prose writings, vitae, correspondence, teaching materials, programs, and clippings.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Pamela Gearhart. Additional content donated by the estate of Livingston Gearhart.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Biographical Note
Livingston Gearhart was born in Buffalo, New York December 31, 1916. His mother was Lillian Hawley Gearhart, a pianist who had studied for a year under Theodor Leschetizky in Vienna. As a child Gearhart studied piano, oboe, violoncello, and sang in church choirs in Buffalo and New York City. He graduated from high school in East Orange, New Jersey in 1935. He entered Curtis Institute of Music in Philadelphia in 1935 as an oboe student of Marcel Tabuteau. In his second year he switched his major to study composition with Rosario Scalero and piano with Nadia Reisenberg.
Gearhart sailed to Paris aboard the Normandie in 1937. With generous support from a wealthy American expatriate, he was able to enroll at the Conservatoire Américain de Fontainebleau where he studied music theory and composition with Nadia Boulanger. He was awarded the school's 2nd prize (no first prize was awarded that year) in the Prix Stovall composition competition in 1937. While in Paris he also met Igor Stravinsky, Darius Milhaud, Robert Casadesus, pianist Isidor Philipp, and his future wife and duo-piano partner, Virginia Clotfelter. He and Virginia performed their debut in Paris February 1, 1939 at the Salle Chopin. They received good reviews and were then able to give concerts in other French and Swiss locations until the conditions of World War II caused them to return to the United States in 1939.
Virginia Clotfelter adopted the professional name Morley and married Gearhart February 28, 1940 in New York City. They worked at numerous venues, including the Hotel Brevoort and the club, Ruban Bleu, both operated by Herbert Jacoby. The pair spent the summers of 1942 and 1943 as Artists-in-Residence at Morley's alma mater, Mills College in Oakland, California. While there Gearhart was able to study composition with Darius Milhaud. The Budapest String Quartet was also in residence at Mills College during those years and Gearhart and Morley formed friendships with quartet members Alexander and Mischa Schneider. The Morley Gearhart duo was very successful, performing works by Milhaud, Norman Dello Joio, David Diamond, and Stravinsky's Concerto per due pianoforte soli.
The duo received contracts with Columbia Concerts and the Fred Waring Show that extended from 1943-1953. During 1941 to 1953, the two-piano team of Morley and Gearhart performed over 2000 concerts throughout the United States and Canada in addition to recording for Columbia Masterworks and Decca Records. Included among the many concert dates was a performance by the duo at the White House for President Dwight D. Eisenhower in 1953. During this period Gearhart also worked as a staff arranger for the Fred Waring Show.
A two-CD retrospective released in 2001, Morley and Gearhart Rediscovered by Ivory Classics, features 22 of Gearhart's two-piano arrangements. Some of these arrangements survive at Penn State in their collection, Fred Waring's America. In many cases Gearhart never fully wrote out his part of a duo so no written arrangement survives.
Livingston Gearhart's output contains several collections written for pedagogical purposes. The first of these works to be published was Clarinet Sessions in 1945. That was followed by similar collections for trumpet, violin, flute, and duos. Gearhart's entire compositional and arranging output includes 400-500 works (counting individual works within the collections).
Gearhart returned to Buffalo in 1955 and was appointed to the faculty of the music department at the University of Buffalo. After a divorce from Virginia Morley, he married violinist and conductor Pamela Gerhart (not a misspelling) in 1955. He taught various courses in keyboard, theory, and orchestration until his retirement in 1985.
Livingston Gearhart had four children: Paul, born to Virginia Morley Gearhart; Kim, Martha, and Fritz, born to Pamela Gearhart. Livingston Gearhart died in Buffalo at the age of 79 on July 14, 1996.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains the prose writings of Livingston Gearhart along with correspondence received by him, materials he compiled for teaching classes, programs, and clippings. Many of the writings consist of personal recollections, some of which Gearhart wrote in response to Virginia Gearhart Waring's request for material for her book, Letters from Fontainebleau and the program notes for the Ivory compact discs. The subjects of these writings include his studies at Curtis Institute of Music in 1935, his studies with Nadia Boulanger in 1937-1939, summaries of different stages of his career and life, and assessments of music education at the college level. More of his thoughts about Nadia Boulanger can be found in his lecture notes for the memorial concert he organized in 1980 (Series VI.). His writings about other people he met include portraits of his mother, Lillian Hawley Gearhart, Igor Stravinsky, Leonard Bernstein, Robert Casadesus, Fred Waring, Darius Milhaud, and Béla Bartók. Other writings with advice about performing were written to one or more of his children. The teaching materials include statements that express much of his philosophy about teaching the practical materials of music from the standpoint of a successful working professional.
Correspondence in the collection includes letters by Louise Talma, Peggy Glanville-Hicks, David Diamond, Richard Arnell, Norman Dello Joio, Vittorio Rieti, Robert Motherwell, Alexandre Tansman, and Marcel Tabuteau. There was a relatively small number of programs and clippings originally included with the collection, ranging from a 1933 performance with his mother through his own memorial concert. These were augmented with the additions received from his estate to include substantial documentation of the career of the Morley and Gearhart piano duo, more family performances, and later performances of compositions and arrangements by Gearhart.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in thirteen series:
I. Personal documents
II. Writings by Livingston Gearhart
III. Correspondence
IV. Teaching materials
V. Programs and clippings
VI. Nadia Boulanger subject folders
VII. Additional personal documents
VIII. Contracts for scores and recordings
IX. Inscribed texts
X. Additional writings and artwork
XI. Additional correspondence
XII. Additional programs, clippings, and publicity
XIII. Works lists
Container List
- Personal documents, 1967-1996, I.; Folders 1-2
  - Curriculum vitae, 1967-1978, 8 items (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes a partial works list with dates.
  - Obituaries, biographies, and memorial service, 1996, 19 items (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes obituaries, death notices, and program of memorial concert.
- Writings by Livingston Gearhart, 1977-1993, II.; Folder 3-52
  Arranged in three subseries:
  A. Biographical
  B. Musical topics
  C. People
  D. Nadia Boulanger
  - Biographical writings, 1977-1993, II. A; Folders 3-12
    Arranged alphabetically by folder title which has been either transcribed from a title on the item or from a first line of text.
    - Curtis memories, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Typescript about Curtis Institute of Music in 1935.
    - Dry bones, undated, 1 item (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Manuscript about working in New York City 1940-1942 and the origination of his arrangement of the tune, Dry bones, which he first heard performed by the Delta Rhythm Boys.
    - From College Street in Bflo (ca. 1925-7)..., undated, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Manuscript recollection of train whistles.
    - In 1940, all nightclub entertainers were required to ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Typescript about working in New York City and people encountered, including club owner Herbert Jacoby, singer Elsie Houston, and harpist Caspar Reardon.
    - In East Orange c. 1930 ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Manuscript recollection of hearing his mother and Lili Balint play piano.
    - Memories, in high school ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Typescript about his teenage years.
    - It's only in my sixties ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Typescript about his parents and upbringing in Buffalo.
    - Memories (1945-46), undated, 1 item (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Typescript about family life during 1945-46.
    - A ship called the Normandie was special to me ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Typescript about the ship on which he sailed to France.
    - When I was a kid, Country Gardens was a popular piano solo, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Typescript about folk songs as musical material, with mention of Percy Grainger.
  - Musical topics, 1977-1993, II. B; Folders 13-31
    - Articles (music) undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Manuscript list.
    - Art & psychology of musical programing, undated, 2 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Typescript.
    - Born into a professional musical family ..., 1977, 1 item (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Typescript about the state of music education in general and at the University at Buffalo.
    - Brahms notes, undated, 4 items (4 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Manuscripts of notes with ideas about articles concerning Johannes Brahms.
    - Hints on zipping thru the program, undated, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Typescript comments about practicing music.
    - The history of the Arts goes back far enough ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Typescript about artistic and educational trends in the twentieth century.
    - How to practice the piano without much profit, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Typescript pointing out common errors in practice technique.
    - It was about 31 years ago, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Typescript about joy in music performance.
    - On teaching, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Typescript about what makes a good teacher.
    - Playing from memory, 1979, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Saint-Saëns lived fourscore years ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Manuscript with comments about composers Saint-Saëns, Chopin, and Milhaud.
    - Searching for the formulas that develop functional keyboard, with no time wasted, undated, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Typescript notes about keyboard skills.
    - Some composer writes piano variations on a theme of Handel ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Typescript notes about tonal keys in music.
    - Some theories about theory, undated, 1 item (4 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Mimeographed typescript notes concerning music theory pedagogy.
    - There are hundreds of talented, ambitious, hard-working soloists ..., 1980, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Photocopied typescript of letter without addressee about the music profession.
    - Unsuccessful syncopation, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Manuscript list of musical examples.
    - Untitled list of musical works, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Variations on an American Air (a joke for musicians) undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Typescript notes on performance of his piece Variations on an American Air: Chautauqua Symphony Orchestra, Walter Hendl, conductor and piano soloist, Aug. 14, 1962.
    - X-number of basic principles of ensemble performance, undated, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Typescript notes to one of his children about musical performance.
  - People, 1977-1993, II. C; Folders 32-44
    Arranged in alphabetical order by person who is subject of the writing. A list of names is in the first folder. It only partially corresponds to the writings in the collection.
    - Personages, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Typescript list.
    - Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990: undated, 3 items (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Two manuscripts and one typescript. One manuscript also contains comments about Antonia Brico.
    - Brico, Antonia: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Casadesus, Robert, 1899-1972: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Dushkin, Samuel, 1891-1976: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 37)
      Typescript. Also contains paragraph about his mother, Lillian Hawley Gearhart.
    - Gearhart, Lillian, b. 1889: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Hutcheson, Ernest, 1871-1951: undated, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Manuscript.
    - Milhaud, Darius, 1892-1974: undated, 3 items (4 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Two typescripts and one manuscript. The manuscript is also about the musical scene in Paris in the late 1930s.
    - Philipp, Isidore, 1863-1958: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Typescript. Also contains one paragraph about Fritz Reiner.
    - Schnabel, Artur, 1882-1951: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Waring, Fred, 1900-1984: undated, 3 items (4 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Typescript and manuscripts.
  - Boulanger, Nadia: 1977-1991, II. D; Folders 45-51
    Arranged alphabetically by document title or first line of text.
    - At Rue Ballu ..., undated, 1 item (5 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Memories of Nadia Boulanger, undated, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Nadia Boulanger, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - She lectured me ..., undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - That woman arranged for my funding by an expatriate affluent American, Atherton Curtis, 1977, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - There is absolutely no trace of memory to explain how I happened to be sitting at Nadia Boulanger's elbow, undated, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - With Nadia, 1991, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1937-1997, III.; Folders 52-97
  Chiefly consists of correspondence received by Livingston Gearhart. Correspondence written by Gearhart can be found in the following folders: James Coover, under Gearhart's name, Pamela Gearhart, C. Paul Herfurth, Harriet Simons, and William Thomson.
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent name.
  - Althouse, Jay: July 26, 1984, September 25, 1986, December 8, 2005, 3 items (4 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Typescripts on behalf of Shawnee Press. 1984 letter addressed to Virginia Waring. Manuscript letter from Pamela Gearhart to Althouse
  - Arnell, Richard, 1917-2009: November 7, 1942, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Manuscript. Mentions possible performance of his work by Sir Thomas Beecham.
  - Boulanger, Nadia: September 5, 1937, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Typescript in French with separate English translation.
  - Bureau de concerts Alfred Lyon: April 1, 1939, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Typescript contract in French for performance with Virginia Clotfelter.
  - Bureau de concerts Marcel de Valmalète: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Typescript contract in French for performance by Virginia Clotfelter at Salle Chopin.
  - Casadesus, Robert, 1899-1972: December 27, 1938, August 23, 1939, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 57)
    1 manuscript, 1 typescript, both in French. 1939 letter written on behalf of Casino de Vichy by unidentified author with additional handwritten note by Casadesus.
  - Coover, James, 1925-2004: circa 1977-1981, 3 items (4 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Typescripts from Livingston Gearhart to James Coover.
  - De Lancie, John, 1921-2002: 1984-1997, 5 items (5 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Typescript letters. The last letter from De Lancie is addressed to Pamela Gearhart. Also includes one unsent, undated letter from Gearhart to De Lancie.
  - Decreus, Camille, 1876-1939: 1939, 3 items (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Manuscript letters in French by the director of the Conservatoire américain de Fontainebleau.
  - Dello Joio, Norman, 1913-2008: undated, November 15, 1951, 2 items (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Manuscripts.
  - Diamond, David, 1915-2005: October 8, 1943, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Manuscript letter with references to Theodore Chanler and Oscar Levant.
  - Diller, Angela, 1877-1968: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Durand, Jacques, Madame, d. 1958: November 1, 1939, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Manuscript letter in French.
  - Dushkin, Samuel, 1891-1976: 1940 or 1941, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Firkušný, Rudolf, 1912-1994: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Gearhart, Livingston: undated, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Typescript addressed to "Diane" without surname.
  - Gearhart, Pamela: undated, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Typescript from Livingston to Pamela; manuscript from Pamela Gearhart to Norma Jean Lamb.
  - Glanville-Hicks, Peggy: November 17, 1942, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Manuscript letter signed "Peggy Bate" with mention of husband Stanley Bate.
  - Harper, Raymond, Mrs.: February 22, 1945, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Herfurth, C. Paul (Clarence Paul), 1893-1988: 1975-1979, 10 items (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Typescript letters; 5 from Herfurth; 4 in response from Livingston Gearhart; 1 from Pamela Gearhart to Herfurth.
  - Hill, Richard S. (Richard Snyder), 1901-1961: November 8, 1944, 1 item (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Typescript addressed to Don E. Cassel care of Livingston Gearhart. Written on Library of Congress Music Division letterhead.
  - Jacoby, Herbert: 1940, 2 items (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Manuscript letters confirming employment of Livingston Gearhart and Virginia Morley at the Hotel Brevoort Supper Club or Le Ruban Bleu club owned by Jacoby.
  - Klein, John, 1915-1981: March 14, 1946, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Lamb, Norma Jean: September 28, 1978, February 12, 1979, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 75)
    1 manuscript and 1 typescript. Typescript written on Buffalo & Erie County Public Library letterhead.
  - Lawton, Dorothy, 1881-1960: February 10, 1945, 1 item (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Manuscript letter on paper with New York Public Library letterhead.
  - MacDermott, Theo: July 12, 1939, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 77)
    Manuscript. Note inserted states that Theo MacDermott was personal secretary to Sir Basil Zaharoff.
  - Massing, Jeanne Jettas: July 4, 1984, 1 item (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Manuscript letter with two small photographs attached: one of the author's mother, the other of Lillian Hawley Gearhart. Also enclosed, one newspaper clipping about a concert in 1933 by Lillian and Livingston Gearhart, with photograph of the pair.
  - Phillips, Benjamin: June 25, 1993, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Pleyel (Firm): March 29, 1939, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Typescript in French.
  - Reinhardt, Aurelia Henry, 1877-1948: circa 1942, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Reisenberg, Nadia: February 18, 1940, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Rieti, Vittorio, 1898-1994: March 30, 1943, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Robertson, Rae, 1893-1956: January 14, 1945, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Manuscript letter marked Urgent, informing Gearhart that the piano duo Bartlett and Robertson would be filling in for concerts for Morley and Gearhart in their absence. The other member of the duo was Ethel Bartlett (1896-1978).
  - Schaeffer, Myron: December 4, 1945, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Section musicale du conseil superieur de la radiodiffusion: July 1939, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Schneider, Alexander, 1908-1993: undated, 3 items (3 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 87)
    Manuscripts. One item possibly by Alexander Schneider's daughter, Natascha.
  - Schneider, Mischa, 1905-1985: August 3, 1946, June 24, 1965, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Shawnee Press: 1988-2005, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 89)
    Correspondence between employees of Shawnee Press and either Livingston or Pamela Gearhart.
  - Simons, Harriet: July 17, 1975, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 90)
    Typescript letter from Gearhart to conductor Harriet Simons concerning planned performance of Gearhart's Dry bones and Gearhart's association with John Cage.
  - Stewart, Reginald: August 28, 1945, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Tabuteau, Marcel, 1887-1966: May 27, 1943, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Talma, Louise, 1906-1996: May 8, 1946, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 93)
    Manuscript with notice of May 11, 1946 performance of her Toccata for Orchestra by the NBC Orchestra.
  - Tansman, Alexandre, 1897-1986: 1943, 2 items (2 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 94)
    Typescripts. One in French.
  - Thomson, William, 1927-: undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 95)
    Typescript by Gearhart to Thomson with manuscript response by Thomson.
  - Waring, Virginia: February 13, 1985, circa 1993, 2 items (6 leaves) (Box 1, Folder 96)
    One item consists of undated notes by Livingston Gearhart to Virginia Waring.
  - Unidentified correspondent, undated, 1 item (1 leaf) (Box 1, Folder 97)
    Manuscript in French.
- Teaching materials, 1955-1985, IV.; Folders 98-104
  These folders contain examples, exercises, and examinations prepared by Gearhart for use in his classes. They also include his notes that critique how the courses are taught and related matters.
  - Basic keyboard class notes, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Basic keyboard class proposals and policies, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Basic keyboard class outlines, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Basic keyboard class music and examinations, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Basic keyboard class assorted documents, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Keyboard harmony, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Orchestration, 1955-1985, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Programs and clippings, 1933-1979, V.; Folders 105-106
  - Programs, 1939-1979, 6 items (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Clippings, 1933-1977, 16 items (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Nadia Boulanger subject folders, 1976-1980, VI.; Folders 107-108
  - Nadia Boulanger memorial concert folder, 1980, 4 items (Box 2, Folder 107)
    Contains program of October 22, 1980 memorial concert held at University at Buffalo, concert announcement, and lecture notes written by Gearhart.
  - Nadia Boulanger clippings, 1976. 1979, 1980, 3 items (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Additional personal documents, 1935-1974, VII.; Folders 109-113
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - East Orange High School (New Jersey) diploma, 24 June 1935, 1 item (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Curtis Institute of Music transcript of grades, 8 March 1955, 2 items (Box 2, Folder 110)
    Dated 8 March 1955, but contains transcript of grades for courses taken 1935-1937.
  - Divorce decree for Livingston and Virginia Gearhart, 1954, 3 items (Box 2, Folder 111)